多谢帮我做大扫除 Malloy
Thanks for helping me with spring cleaning, Malloy.
这本漫画有点诡异啊《三K侠》?
This is a weird comic book. Klan Man?
3K党: 宣扬白人至上和基督恐怖主义的邪教组织 活动时围观焚烧的十字架
《三K侠》啊
Oh, Klan Man.
跨越长空 漂洋过海
Across the air, across the sea,
十字架烧进你家草坪
And a cross on your lawn.
你真该看看那个被处死的妹子 火辣爆了
Oh, you should've seen lynch lady. Ooh, she was a real piece of ass.
哇 居然还卖这么多酷玩意儿
Whoa. Look at all this cool stuff you can buy.
透视眼镜 间谍笔 海猴子?
X-ray glasses, spy pens, sea monkeys,
货真价实的太空船只要两刀?
And a real rocket ship for only two bucks?
哎呀 Malloy
Oh, Malloy.
那些糊弄小孩的垃圾也就图个新鲜 没一样是好使的
It's all novelty bullshit to trick little kids. None of that crap ever worked.
这里是美利坚 没人敢给假货打广告的
This is America. They couldn't advertise something if it wasn't true.
喂 新鲜玩意儿店
Aah! Novelty bullshit.
Lou 咱来订单了
Lou, we got an order!
漫迪字幕组倾情奉献
脆莓公园
♢ 挺高兴 ♢ 偏执绝非过错
♢ 井脑湿 ♢ 白云苍狗
♢ 旗木 联合译制
早 林警们 今天团队凝聚力训练的主题是:
Morning, rangers. For today's bonding exercise,
每个人都来完成以下句子:
I want each of you to finish this sentence--
Connie太丑了...
Connie is so ugly...
她丑瞎了镜子
Her mirror went blind!
莉娜·杜汉姆都觉得她裸体很恶心
Lena Dunham thinks she looks gross naked.
美剧《衰姐们》女主兼导演
我的自慰JJ都硬不起来
My dildo went limp.
我讨厌今天的训练
I hate these exercises.
这叫"团队建设" Connie
It's called "team building," Connie.
各位知道
As you know,
本周末脆莓将举办一场面向游艇土豪的赛船会
this weekend Brickleberry is hosting a regatta for super-rich yacht owners.
那几天会是老子阿谀奉承土豪的好机会
It's my chance to suck golden b-hole for a few days
没准他们会邀请我去豪宅一游
And get invited to their fancy villas.
你们的任务是确保...
Your job is to make sure
这些土豪不会在公园里见到半个讨人厌的穷鬼
these rich people don't see any disgusting poor people in the park.
我们怎么赶走穷人啊?
How do we get rid of the poor people?
上帝用的是飓风
God used katrina.
公园里要藏的穷人多了去了
There's too many poor people in this park to hide.
他们每周末都会到河里漂流
They tube down the river every weekend.
所以你和Connie要把河道堵住
That's why you and Connie are gonna dam it up
用这些玩意儿
With these.
从《储备战》低价拍卖来的利比亚储备
Got 'em for a steal on Libyan Storage Wars.
储备战: 真人秀 规则为三个月不缴租 仓库里的东西就会被拍卖
这样不好吧 Woody 这种东西好像有辐射
I don't know, Woody. Those look radioactive.
就算没辐射 你也照样会是绿巨人
But if it wasn't for radiation, you'd still be Bruce Banner.
Steve Ethel 去用直升机...
Steve, Ethel, take the helicopter
把那帮穷鬼的拖车统统移出公园
And remove all the white-trash trailers from the park.
我不能坐直升机
I can't go in the helicopter!
- 说啥? 为毛不能? - 好怕怕的
- What? Why the hell not? - It's scary.
比这个还怕怕嘛?
Scarier than this?
老子就凭这一根手指 能变出七种花样玩死你
I can kill a man in seven different ways with this finger.
好啦 人家坐还不行嘛 拜托别拿手指玩我
Okay! I'll go in the chopper! Just don't finger me!
超爱《飞狼》那部剧
I loved that episode of Airwolf.
90年代美剧 主角是一架性能凶悍的直升机
话说直升机具体怎么把拖车都弄出去啊?
So how exactly is a helicopter going to get the trailers out?
Woody买了这块巨型"大笨狼怀特"磁铁
Woody bought this giant Wile E. Coyote magnet.
乐一通卡通角色 使用相似磁铁
钥匙给你 空运的时候可不许吓晕了
Here you go. Oh, try not to faint when we're airborne.
你要我开这玩意儿? 你自己怎么不开?
You want me to fly this thing? Why can't you?
两个原因 第一 我因为醉酒驾机被吊销执照了
Two reasons--one, I lost my license for flying drunk,
第二 我正醉着呢
And, two, I'm drunk.
不行
I can't!
真怂逼
What a pussy.
发生上次那样的事 我不可能再开飞机
There's no way I can fly again after what happened last time.
求救 求救
Mayday! Mayday!
我不想死啊
I don't want to die!
你就吐在里面了么 大叔?
Did you just throw up in there, mister?
just有"刚刚"和"仅仅"双意
谁说"就"? 我不仅吐
No, I didn't just throw up.
还拉了一裤兜子
I also shit myself.
怎么原地不动啊?
Why ain't we moving?
所以昨晚我女朋友说她想整舒服点
So last night when my girl said she wanted to slip into something more comfortable,
我不知道她是昏过去了
I didn't know she meant a coma.
嘿 你怎么不笑? 很搞笑好不
Hey, what's wrong with you? That's funny.
虽然也很悲惨 因为她挂了
I mean, it's sad, too, 'cause she died.
我烦透被人说丑了 Denzel
I'm sick of being called ugly, Denzel.
女孩子家承受不住如此对待
There's only so much a girl can take.
总有一天 我会爆发的 到时候...
One day I'm gonna snap, and when I do--
淡定 至少还有我欣赏你呢
Calm down. At least I appreciate you.
- 真的? - 当然
- Really? - Sure.
你这种丑逼的存在才会让我这种帅逼更招人喜欢
Ugly people like you exist to make people appreciate handsome people like me.
我真是受够了
I've had enough of this!
干嘛呢你?
What are you doing?
我在救你啊
I was saving your life.
下次让我死就是了 我们这是在哪儿?
Next time let me die! Where the hell are we?
像是个荒岛
Looks like a deserted island.
卧槽 跟我梦里一模一样的
Damn, it's just like my dream,
只不过你不是克劳斯·利特曼 也没她的丰润花穴
Only you ain't Cloris Leachman with a hot wing for a clitoris.
美国电视明星 现年84岁
我害怕 Denzel
I'm scared, Denzel.
要是没人发现咱们怎么办?
What if no one ever finds us here?
我不要没破处就死 除非...
I'll die a virgin! Unless...
谢了 我会在你处女葬礼上特伤心特伤心的
Yeah, I'm gonna be real sad at your virgin funeral.
嘿 你动俺的房子是要干毛?
Hey, what the hell you doing to my house?
Woody要你们这些穷鬼消失 我得移走你的拖车
Woody wants all you poor people gone, so I was trying to tow your trailer.
这是个拖车房
This is a mobile home.
不是用来挪东挪西的
It ain't designed to be moved.
用直升机吊着大磁铁来不是更省事?
Wouldn't a helicopter and a Wile E. Coyote magnet work better?
没错 你说得对 但人家好怕飞了啦
Yes. Yes, it would, but I'm too afraid to fly.
话说我和Bobby也有过焦虑困扰
You know, me and bobby used to have anxiety issues too.
真的?
Really?
是啊 我过去有幽闭恐惧症 旷野恐惧症 和不间断的死亡恐惧症
Yep. I had claustrophobia, agoraphobia, and a constant fear of mortality.
我过去总干山羊
And I used to [bleep] goats.
后来唐人街一个催眠大师把我们治好了
Then we saw a hypnotist in chinatown who cured us.
现在我是个状态奇佳 非常正常的山羊奸夫了
Now I'm a well-adjusted, perfectly normal sheep [bleep].
那是我最喜欢的朗地·特维斯的歌
That's my favorite Randy Travis song.
美国乡村歌手 此处恶搞乡村音乐
干洗 催眠
没错 我就是陈先生 能为您效劳吗?
Yes, me Mr. Chen. What I do for you?
我要你给我催眠
I want you to hypnotize me.
顺便这条裤子的污渍死活弄不掉
Also, I have a stain I can't get out.
这么多"巧口力"怎么弄到裤子上的?
How you get this much "chocorate" on your pants?
恶搞亚洲人口音
直升机事故 我来也是为这事儿
Helicopter accident. That's why I'm here.
我要你助我成为一名勇敢的飞行员
I need you to make me a fearless pilot.
没问题 现在洗衣/催眠买一赠一
Okay. I give you two for one-pants and trance combo.
说实话 不知道如此强健的大脑...
To be honest, I doubt a strong mind like this
能不能被催...
Can even be hypnoti--
这个古老的汉字代表英勇
This ancient Chinese symbol of courage.
只要把它挂在脖子上
As "rong" as you wear it around your neck,
你就会成为勇敢的"机湿"
You will be a brave "pirot,"
机师 恶搞亚洲人口音
无畏的"机湿"
A "fearress pirot"!
吖 我是一名勇敢的海盗
Argh! I'm a fearless pirate!
Steve误听亚洲口音
不 不是海盗 是"机湿"
No! Not pirate! "pirot"!
Denzel 事先提醒你
Denzel, just so you know,
如果你突然暴毙 我会吃掉你的
If you die suddenly, I'm going to eat you.
我的天 Connie 快看
Oh, my god! Connie, look at this!
但愿是富客汉堡店 但愿是富客汉堡店
Please be a fatburger. Please be a fatburger.
美国连锁快餐
我的天
Oh, my--
好啊 美女们
Hello, ladies.
多么美如冠玉的尤物啊
What a magnificent creature.
是很屌 对不对?
It is nice, isn't it?
没说你 猥琐男
Not you, rat face!
是这个红发女神
The red-haired goddess.
你瞎了吧?
You blind, right?
欢迎来到蕾丝岛 美人儿
Welcome to lesbo island, beautiful one.
请问有何吩咐?
How can we serve you?
这太假了 我没做梦吧
This can't be real. I must be dreaming.
来人掐掐我
Somebody pinch me.
我说"掐" 是让你对我用金手指 直到我高潮如涌 湿了你胸
When I said "pinch," I meant finger-blast till I squirt all over your breasts.
唉 三陪公司不乐意派人给我
Oh, the escort service cut me off
因为他们都觉得我是"长着死鱼眼的怪胎"
'cause they claim I'm a "dead-eyed weirdo."
我都不知道那啥意思
Whatever that means.
所以你明天得在欢迎会上陪我
So you're gonna be my date to the welcoming party tomorrow.
给我穿上你最暴露的衣服
I want you to wear your sluttiest dress
而且要表现得对我欲火焚身
And act like you want to bone me.
恶心
Ew, gross.
想去吃猫粮为生吗? 你不这样做我就炒了你
Would you rather have to eat cat food? 'Cause you'll be unemployed!
住手 流氓 放开那位女士
Avast, ye scoundrel. Unhand that lass!
搞毛线? 同性恋自豪日到了嘛?
What the [bleep]? Is it gay pride day already?
Steve?
请叫我Steve船长 我丰满的女士
Captain Steve, me buxom beauty--
我乃七大洋中最勇武的海盗
The bravest pirate in all the seven seas.
- 去吃药吧 Steve - 小心了 指挥官...
- Oh, cut the shit, Steve. - Take heed, commander...
因为我将掠夺你的土地
For me intention be to plunder yer land,
无论是肉体还是金钱上的战利品都将一网打尽
Looking for booty of the flesh or coin.
- 我的天 - 别搞笑 Steve
- Oh, my. - I mean it, Steve!
老子没时间听你在这儿神神叨叨的 给我打住
I don't have time for this happy horseshit! Stop it!
别乱说话 旱鸭子 不然拿命来偿
Watch ye mouth, landlubber, or pay with ye life.
不要逼我对你用一阳指
Don't make me pull out the kill finger!
我的一阳指 你竟然把它剁了
Aah! My kill finger-you killed it!
我靠 真特么滑
Damn it! Slippery piece of--
一会儿我将以更潇洒的姿势归来
I'll be back for a better look later.
我已经咸湿得像进了机场餐厅的瑞贝尔·威尔森一样了
I'm wetter than Rebel Wilson at an airport Cinnabon.
美国明星 体形肥胖
掉哪去了? 掉哪去了?
Where is it? Where is it?
靠 为啥我桌子下有这么多断指?
Shit, why are there so many severed fingers under my desk?
听好了
Mark me words--
冒犯Steve船长那天起 后悔种子已在你心中播下
ye will rue the day ye crossed swords with captain Steve.
我们开战了
This be war.
别再说黑人英语了
Stop talking in Ebonics!
这笔账我一定会千刀万剐你 Steve
Ooh, I'm gonna get you for this, Steve!
我擦嘞
God damn it!
透视眼镜
这透视眼镜居然有用
These x-ray glasses work!
不 眼镜没用 是我没穿
No, they don't. I'm naked.
Denzel和Connie都死哪去了? 他们本该现在来的
Where the hell are Denzel and Connie? They should be here.
Connie要来?
Connie's coming?
我不冒这个险了
Not worth the risk.
还有那狗日的Steve
And that goddamn Steve--
好在他没砍掉我最喜欢的指头
Good thing he didn't get my favorite finger.
我去你大爷 他脑子被驴踢了是咋的?
Jesus Christ! What the [bleep] is his problem?
他去了趟Bobby Possumcods的催眠师那 现在觉得自己是海盗
He thinks he's a pirate 'cause he went to Bobby Possumcods' hypnotist.
那我得找到这个催眠师 让他在Steve毁掉赛船会前
Well, I got to find this hypnotist and get him to snap Steve out of it
把Steve给弄清醒
Before he screws up my regatta.
那家伙住在唐人街什么地方
The guy's somewhere in Chinatown.
- 他叫啥? - 不知道 不过我可以给你画幅肖像
- What's his name? - I don't know. But I'll draw you a picture.
见过此人吗? 提供线索者奖励500美金
嘿 这是你吗?
Hey, this you?
你在家乡一定受万人敬仰吧
You must be worshipped where you come from.
你从头到脚趾再到骆驼趾 都散发着迷人的气息
You're beautiful from head to toe to camel toe.
谢谢 我能用骆驼趾捡铅笔呢
Thanks. I can pick up a pencil with it.
- 想见识见识吗? - 不 打住
- Want to see? - Nope, that's okay!
闭嘴 丑男 这儿不欢迎你
Shut up, ugly man! You're not welcome here.
美丽的人啊 我知道在你面前 我们都太不起眼
Beautiful one, I know we're all so plain next to you,
但我们中有人能让你...
But do any of us appeal to you...
- 燃起欲火吗? - 开什么玩笑?
- Sexually? - Are you kidding me?
让我上你们谁我都乐意啊
I'd give my left lip to do any of you!
- 选我 - 不 选我
- Pick me! - No, me!
我的舌头能把树皮都舔掉
I can lick the bark off a tree!
够了 为了维持安定
Stop! To keep the peace,
她只要从我们这里选一人同床即可
She will choose just one of us to sleep with.
嘿 Connie 我手机貌似有信号了
Hey, Connie, I think my cell phone's working!
噢 给我看看
Ooh, let me see it.
为了不让傻缺Steve船长闯进来 我都雇保安了
I had to hire security guards to keep captain asshole Steve out of here.
我倒觉得他蛮有魅力
Well, I think he's charming.
还有 他砍掉你手指的时候太搞笑了
Plus, it was pretty hilarious when he cut off your fingers,
虽然你手指看起来不是太妙
Which aren't looking so good.
这是我的手指 Ethel 我是不会放弃它们的
These are my fingers, Ethel, and I'm not giving up on them!
它们会长回去的
They are gonna take root!
作为游艇协会会长 我不得不说
As head of the yachting association, I have to say,
如果比赛能和这宴会一样出彩的话
If the regatta comes out nearly as well as this party,
我希望明年能与你在澳大利亚再会
I want you to join us next year in Australia.
太棒了 我都等不及去尝尝那些...
Great. I can't wait to try one of those...
- 生机勃勃的洋葱了 - 很好
- Bloomin' onions. - Splendid.
那这位漂亮的小姐是?
And who is this lovely creature?
我的女伴 她想上我
Oh, my date. She wants to bone me.
是啊 死鱼眼胖子真让我湿了一身
Yeah. Dead-eyed fatties turn me on so hard.
看? 我说吧
See? I told you.
如果她是我的女伴 我真想好好的摸上她一把呢
Well, if she were my date, I couldn't keep my hands off her.
是嘛? 好吧 来吧
Oh, yeah? Well, go ahead.
在她的胸前来上一把吧 她不会介意的
Give them sweater stretchers a squeeze. She don't care.
我介意
I do care!
既然她不介意...
Well, as long as she doesn't care...
把手拿开 龌龊鬼
Hands off her, ye mangy bilge rat!
我擦嘞 又是海盗Steve
God damn it, it's pirate Steve!
- 你没事吧 女士? - 我现在没事了
- Are ye okay, lass? - I am now.
这海盗真是扫我的兴
This pirate is a cockblocker.
女士是用来取悦的 不是用来猥亵的 先生
A lady is to be pleased, not squeezed, sir.
就用你的金表当学费吧
The cost of that lesson be yer gold piece.
后会有期
Till we meet again.
他尼玛从哪儿学的这一套?
How the hell does he do that?
听好了 朋友们 我需要一群海员
Hear this, me hearties! I need a crew.
暴君Woody和他那群自封的帝国主义流氓们
The tyrant Woody and his scourge of entitled imperialists
正致力从这公正的土地上铲除贫苦百姓
Are endeavoring to rid this fair land of its poor,
反抗他们的暴政 吾辈义不容辞
So it be our duty to rid them of their fineries!
他啥意思?
What'd he say?
他说俺们应该去夺取暴君的财宝 Bobby
He said we must prey upon the golden galleons of the oppressor, Bobby.
哦 好哒 可以搞强奸吗?
Oh, okay. Do we get to rape?
可惜 海盗们不再奸淫
Alas, pirates don't rape anymore.
靠 真失望
Aw. Oh, man.
倒是最新那部《加勒比海盗》
Except for the last Pirates of the Caribbean,
真还强奸了观众们的眼睛
Which raped the eyes of the audience.
至少咱们还可以劫掠嘛
Well, at least we get to pillage!
对 汝等愿追随我否?
Aye. Are ye with me?
那必须的
Hell, yeah!
流浪汉Larry强奸过一罐热豆子
Hobo Larry raped a warm can of beans once.
对 "日豆人"就是我啦
Yep, I was porkin' beans.
褐丘古炮台
Jim 你个畜生养的
Jim, you goddamn son of a bitch!
你们这些混蛋要绑我去哪?
Where are you mother[bleep] taking me?
Jim
Jim!
献给你 吾爱
For ye, me lovely.
Steve船长 真漂亮
Oh, Captain Steve, it's beautiful.
嘿 那项链是我的
Hey, that's my diamond necklace!
你们这帮鸟人
Ye son of a bitch!
若是别人问起 谁人劫了汝辈
If anyone asks who just robbed ye,
告诉他们 Steve船长是也
Tell 'em captain Steve.
没强奸你们也别往心里去啊
And don't take it personal that we didn't rape y'all.
我们心里也憋得慌呢
We're trying to cut back.
你美呆了
You're amazing!
等一下
Wait. Hmm.
腿间距只有一英寸
Only a one-inch thigh gap.
下一个
Next!
靠啊 Connie 干啥这么挑剔?
Damn, Connie, why you being so picky?
处女膜我只有一个 Denzel
I only have one hymen, Denzel.
姑娘快被你挑完了 你最好赶紧的 挑个能搞的完事了
Well, we're running out of girls, so you better hurry up and choose a cooz.
甭担心 有称心的我一眼就看得出来
Don't worry. I'll know when the right one comes along.
行吧 下一位是Alexa
All right. Next we have Alexa.
Connie 你没事吧?
Connie, are you okay?
请把遮羞布掀起来
Lift your loincloth, please.
简直完美
It's perfect.
就像火腿片做成的玫瑰一样
Like a rose made of prosciutto.
Malloy 那些有钱的娘炮成天追着我屁股...
Malloy, those rich pole smokers are crawling up my ass
要我解决Steve和他那帮抢钱的死海狗
about Steve and his thieving band of salty shit-dogs.
我得把他和他那艘破船都弄走
I got to get him and his stupid ship out of here!
我们用这艘北极星核潜艇把那船轰飞怎么样?
Why don't we blow it up with this polaris nuclear sub?
能发射真鱼雷 而且只要6.98刀咧
It fires real torpedoes, and it's only $6.98!
那特么是硬纸板做的好吧 Malloy
It's made of [bleep] cardboard, Malloy!
这又是搞毛?
What the hell was that?
我勒个去
Holy shit.
老子的房被轰烂了 你们这群疯杂种
You blew up my house, you crazy son of a bitch!
请你...
Please...
收下吾深深的歉意
Accept this as my apology.
老天爷 我该怎么办才好?
Oh, god. What am I gonna do?
我们来领酬金的
We here for reward.
- 你们里面有催眠师吗? - 我不是
- Are any of you a hypnotist? - No.
- 不是我 - 我也不是
- No, not me. - No, no, no.
我卖大魔怪哟
I sell mogwais.
都特么滚粗
Get the hell out of here!
一大帮中国人对我有啥用处?
What am I supposed to do with a Chinese army?
我上了个海的 有戏
Oh, holy Shanghai, that's it!
Steve想扮海盗 老子就陪他扮到底
If Steve wants to play pirate, we'll play pirate.
海盗? 我们不会开"灰机"的
Pirate? We can't fly a "prane."
你们连听力都带口音吗?
So you even hear with an accent?
呣呣 Alexa
Mmm. Alexa.
呣呣 火腿片
Mmm. Prosciutto.
Connie 醒醒 是我
Connie, wake up! It's me!
我要趁大家都睡着 溜到海边做个木筏逃命
I'm gonna sneak to the beach while everyone's asleep and build a raft to escape.
你要走? 为毛?
You're leaving? Why?
这里的事情有点蹊跷 我觉得咱们可能有危险
There's something weird going on here. I think we might be in danger.
你就是嫉妒现在我成了美人 你成了丑逼
You're just jealous because now I'm beautiful and you're the ugly one.
- 随便你怎么想 老子要闪人了 - 好啊
- Look, whatever! I'm out of here! - Fine!
等下 Denzel 帮我把这个捎给Alexa好不?
Wait, Denzel. Can you give this to Alexa for me?
削木是我的新手艺
I've taken up whittling.
嘿 你是男的 男人怎么会...
Hey, you're a man! What's a man doin--
♪ 呦吼吼 来瓶兰姆酒 ♪
♪ yo, ho, ho, and a bottle of rum ♪
♪ 去趟动物园 哥要日到腿抖 ♪
♪ let's swing by the zoo, I need to get some ♪
我爱死当海盗了 终于可以自己擦屁股啦
I love being a pirate! I can finally wipe myself!
谁开车送我去医院?
Can somebody drive me to the hospital?
每人拿一把忍匕
Everybody grab a ginsu.
搞毛...
What the...?
谁想吃点豆不?
Uh, anybody want some beans?
你们找谁么?
Ha ha! Looking for someone?
嘿 傻缺 埋伏得不错啊
Hey, dumbass, nice ambush.
我们人数多你们三倍
We outnumber you three to one.
那是老天爷眷顾我们正好杀个痛快咯
Then I'd say the odds are squarely in our favor.
对吧 伙计们?
Right, mateys?
只剩您与在下一决生死了
Now it's just ye and me.
弄死他 Steve船长
Get him, Captain Steve!
走跳板吧 肥冬瓜
Now walk the plank, fatscallion.
海盗惩虐俘虏的一种方式 也有让某人下台的意思
永别了 残酷世界
Good-bye, cruel world!
老子脚踝碎了
I broke my goddamn ankles!
在下领赏来了
And now for me reward.
你真勇敢 Steve船长
You're so brave, Captain Steve.
有空你应该来宿舍找我玩
You should come by my cabin later.
看来即便他盔甲护体 我也有机可乘
Ha ha! Looks like I found a chink in his armor.
chink指弱点 亦是用来侮辱亚裔的词汇
- 说谁呢你? - 打比方而已 没骂你
- Hey, what the hell? - Figure of speech-- Don't get offended.
我的天
Blimey!
再临打折卡?
One free fluff and fold?
我在哪? 怎么被吊起来了?
Where am I? Why am I upside down?
Steve船长 你这海盗菊花就等着被爆烂吧
Captain Steve, your pirate ass is about to be [bleep] in the bunghole.
我不在时 你们这群变态就玩这个啊?
So this is what you freaks do when I'm not around?
你在房子下面造了一个凌辱密室?
You built a sex dungeon under your cabin?
这比普通地下室实用一百倍好吧
Well, it's a lot more practical than a basement.
再说要是需要普通地下室 撤了这些道具就行了
And if I ever need a regular dungeon, I just take out the dildos.
那你为什么把我关起来?
But why are you locking me up?
因为我想让赛船会正常进行
Because I need this regatta to go well,
我不允许Steve船长像个抽风海盗一样四处捣乱
And I can't have captain Steve running around like a crazy [bleep] pirate!
我是海盗?
I was a pirate?
快进去
Get in there.
Hilda 今儿算你走运 你可以走了
Hilda, it's your lucky day. You're free to go.
经过了12年的凌辱 我真的可以走了?
I can really go, just like that after 12 years?
Hilda 不要把这些年的事放在心上
Hilda, don't let this experience define you.
你正好赶上见证这神奇的海猴子
You're just in time to enter the wonderful world of amazing sea monkeys.
就这玩意? 和包装盒上的半点也不像啊
That's it? It doesn't look anything like the box.
Malloy 我... 告诉过你的
Malloy, I-I tried to tell you.
你知道最操蛋的是啥不?
You know what the worst part is?
你真能说对那么一两次
That you were actually right about something for once.
这玩意真扯淡
This stuff is bullshit.
接下来 各位拥有令我垂涎已久度假村的土豪朋友们
And now, my wealthy friends with vacation homes in places I would like to visit,
迎接咱们期待已久的时刻: 脆莓赛船会
the moment we've been waiting for-- The Brickleberry Regatta!
脆莓赛船会
各就各位 预备...
On your mark, get set...
终点
- 什么情况? - 我勒个去 和包装盒上的一模一样
- What the hell? - Holy shit! It does look like the box!
我就说这玩意儿好使
I told you this stuff works!
承认吧 Woody 只有一个英雄勇敢到能对抗这个怪物
Face it, Woody-there's only one hero brave enough to fight this monster.
- 3K侠? - Steve船长
- Klan Man? - Captain Steve!
求求你 你们不能这么对待Connie
Please! Y'all can't do this to Connie!
准备好和选定的佳人翻云覆雨了吗?
Are you ready to mate with your chosen one?
你说呢? 我湿了一路了
What do you think? I'm leaving a snail trail.
天啊
Oh, my god.
准备好上我了吗 Connie?
Are you ready for me, Connie?
快过来
Come here.
我不能
I can't.
啊? 为什么?
What? Why not?
因为...
Because...
你... 是个... 丑逼
You're... So... Ugly!
是的 Connie 这里是《你是个丑逼》
That's right, Connie. This is You're So Ugly!
专门让不受欢迎的人出糗的真人秀节目
The reality show that humiliates unattractive people!
但...
But...
我们本来准备恶搞别人的 谁料...
We were going to punk Some other beast, but then...
你们被冲上了岸 制作组简直不相信我们的运气
you washed up onshore, and we couldn't believe our luck.
你是说我不能上Alexa了?
You mean I'm not having sex with Alexa?
醒醒吧 真以为你这种丑逼能上她这样的尤物?
Oh, come on, did you really think someone like you could get someone like her?
对不起 Connie 我没能阻止这些变态
Sorry, Connie. I couldn't stop these sick bastards.
"变态"? 我们只是在满足美国人民的需要
"sick"? Hey, we're just giving america what it wants.
没什么比恶搞别人更能赚收视
Nothing gets ratings like degrading people,
遇上Connie这种丑八怪就更是如此了
Especially a hideous, trout-faced monster like Connie.
- 对吧 女士们? - 是啊
- Am I right, ladies? - Yeah!
就在那儿
There it is!
我擦嘞 那是个啥?
Holy shit! What is that?
是海怪
It's the sea monster!
你刚说的是"海猴"
You said "sea monkey."
我还准备要拿吃的撑死它 这玩意儿我可打败不了
I was planning to overfeed it to death. I can't fight that thing.
你肯定行的
Sure you can.
你是Steve船长 毫无畏惧的海盗
You're captain Steve, the fearless pirate.
Ethel 事实是...
Ethel, the truth is,
我只能在催眠师给我戴上勋章之后才变得毫无畏惧
I was only fearless because a hypnotist put a medallion around my neck.
没那玩意 我什么也不是
Without that, I'm nothing.
不 Steve 英勇事迹不是勋章做出来的
No, Steve, the medallion didn't do brave things.
是你啊
You did.
现在你要相信自...
Now it's time to believe in yoursel--
救命 Steve 救命
Help, Steve! Help!
大伙都没事的
You're in no danger!
这只是娱乐表演的一部分
This is all part of the entertainment!
特效超赞有没有?
Great special effects, huh?
卧槽
Shit!
救命
Help!
Steve 我就知道你很勇敢的
Steve, I knew you were brave.
人家要死了
I'm gonna die.
要死了啦
I'm gonna die!
不好
Ah, bad idea!
真棒 我要再订点这玩意儿
Yes! I got to order more of these!
嘿 Steve船长 别来无恙啊?
Hey, captain Steve! What's up?
大伙 你们还活着 我要把你们救出去
Men, you're alive! I'm gonna get you out of here.
- 不用 我们很喜欢这里 - 啥?
- No, we like it here. - What?
两分钟前 我们组成了自己的微型乌托邦社会
In the last two minutes, we formed our own little utopian society.
和四健会一样 只是没那么多xxoo
It's like the 4-h club with less [bleep]!
四健会: 美国农业部农业合作推广体系组织的非营利性青年组织
伙计们 如果不出去 胃酸迟早会把我们消化掉的
Guys, if we don't get out, the stomach acid will eat through our skin.
我说我脚上怎么没肉了呢
Well, that explains the skeleton foot.
有主意了 大家快到大炮上来
I've got it! Everybody get on the cannon.
遵命 船长
Aye, aye, captain.
Steve 你太勇敢了 真不敢相信你活着出来了
Steve, that was so brave! I can't believe you survived.
天呐 你说得对
Oh, my god, you're right.
我差点死了
I almost died!
现在可以来一炮了吧
At least we can have sex now.
抱歉之前说你丑 Connie
I'm sorry I ever called you ugly, Connie.
没关系啦 你都试着帮我了
That's okay. At least you tried to look out for me.
嘿 你觉得我过激了吗?
Hey, do you think I overreacted?
才没
No.
可怜的Jim没能活着出来
Poor Jim didn't make it out alive.
再来 再来 比六面旗游乐园还好玩啊
Again! Again! That's better than [bleep] Six Flags!
六面旗: 美国主题公园连锁品牌
那帮土豪快去死吧
Screw those rich bastards.
既然赶不走穷鬼 就让穷鬼们全都来吧
If we can't keep the poor out, let 'em pour in.
吖 快来吧 穷人们
Argh! Step right up, ye poor people!
来玩沉没的海猴子
Ride the sunken monkey!
Woody船长穷鬼水上公园